CAROL D'SILVA

MULTIMEDIA ARTIST

caroldsillva@yahoo.com











Bengaluru, India

PROFILE

.....

A senior in high school with a profound interest in design and more than three years of experience. The individual is proficient in photo/video editing and animation. Currently working as a freelancer after learning from software-certified instructors.

SOFTWARE SKILLS (DESIGN)

Blender

.....

Adobe Premiere Pro CC

Adobe After Effects CC

Adobe Animate CC

Adobe Illustrator CC

Adobe Audition CC

Adobe Photoshop CC

Spark AR Studio

SOFTWARE SKILLS (PRODUCTIVITY/PROGRAMMING)

Microsoft office

Python & Django

Mysql

Html/CSS

React JS

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

UI/UX Design

.....

November 2020 - January 2022

Created and designed a website called 'Medical Journal'. Worked both on the front end and back end of the website using programming languages(python, java, HTML, and CSS).

- Designed a useful and elegant digital experience for a website helping in the field of medicine and healthcare from start to finish(research, design, test, implement) as the lead.
- In less than 2 months designed eloquent flow and structure of the website along with a fully functioning module for communication
- Fostered collaboration and consistency alongside team members.
- Presented website to a board of members, answering questions and receiving feedback for the same.

Website report: https://bit.ly/3uhOowG

Augmented Reality Developer July 2021 - Present

- Created augmented reality filters and effects for use on Facebook, Instagram, and messenger.
- Integrated 3D elements into world scenes to create an immersive digital experience.
- Worked alongside content creators to cater to their AR needs and ideas.
- Increased impressions to over 160 million and opens to over 32 million in less the one year.

EDUCATION

••••••

Primary, Middle, Secondary Schooling

Lake Montfort School, 2010-2020 Bengaluru _____

AISSE Examination. Passed with distinction.

Higher Secondary Schooling

CMR National Public School, Bengaluru 2020-2022

AISSCE Examination. Passed with distinction.

SOFT SKILLS

Communication Skills

Problem Solving Skills

Collaborative Skills

Presentation Skills

Leadership Skills

Creativity

Adaptability

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Kannada

Konkani

French

Video Editor

May 2021 - Present

- Provided digitization and editing of podcast videos for influencers while meeting tight deadlines.
- Also edited the podcast to be online on popular streaming platforms such as Spotify, anchor, and RSS.
- Worked on Apple and Windows 10/11 computers.
- Worked closely with influencers and worked on merchandise designing from stickers to Tshirts.
- Created video trailers for use on YouTube.
- Edited music videos and lyric videos for musical artists.
- Cinematic travel video and vlogs for influencers as well as social media content like posts/reels.

Photo Editor

May 2021 - Present

- Time managed the photo editing process between curating, editing, labeling, approving, uploading, reediting, and archiving. Maintained image quality while cropping, color correcting, sizing, and retouching
- Assigning/Editing/processing incoming content for internal & mp; external clients
- Restoring/recovering images for clients and colorizing images in order to re-imagine the past.
- Created movie/short film posters.
- Created Thumbnail for youtube and social media post.

REFERENCES

References are available upon request.